let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which component is used to compile, debug and execute the java programs?",
    answer: "JDK",
    options: [
      "JRE",
      "JIT",
      "JDK",
      "JVM"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following is not a Java feature?",
    answer: "Use of pointers",
    options: [
      "Object-oriented",
      "Use of pointers",
      " Portable",
      "Dynamic and Extensible"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Which of these cannot be used for a variable name in Java?",
    answer: "keyword",
    options: [
      "identifier & keyword",
      "identifier",
      "keyword",
      "none of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the extension of java code files?",
    answer: ".java",
    options: [
      ".js",
      ".txt",
      ".jv",
      ".java"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not an OOPS concept in Java?",
    answer: "Compilation",
    options: [
      "Compilation",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Inheritance",
      "Polymorphism"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of polymorphism in Java Programming?",
    answer: "Compile time polymorphism",
    options: [
      "Multiple polymorphism",
      "Compile time polymorphism",
      "Multilevel polymorphism",
      "Execution time polymorphism"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of these are selection statements in Java?",
    answer: "if()",
    options: [
      "break",
      "continue",
      "if()",
      "for()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?",
    answer: "Object class",
    options: [
      "ArrayList",
      "Abstract class",
      "Object class",
      "String"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?",
    answer: "try",
    options: [
      "check",
      "throw",
      "catch",
      "try"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which one of the following is not an access modifier?",
    answer: "Void",
    options: [
      "Protected",
      "Void",
      "Public",
      "Private"
    ]
  },
];